Ajay Ajay
Ajay
Hello Hello friends today's video is going to be quite
expensive because today I have
got the IT cell
number from here behind the Kunvathal here a lot of this decision has been taken
in Wendy you can see here
we will translate it here and
keep it translated what comes out from inside
let's open it a little
now I am discharging it in a simple way
because
a simple cricket I am opening it
because it is quite a
good packing is coming out here so
far the victory path of truth has been good and
we have slowed it down and we are relaxed I
feel that I have seen it, I have opened it and done the
branding here you
can see so I am creating a straight A like this
and here you can see that you will
find some big polythenes here
so there are big polythenes
you can see a fair in the light itself because you can see
two politicians
[Music]
so sometimes it is good that this has been found in the fair such a thing has come
from the phone number of
your  The umbrella is very
nice,
how was the branding of ICICI Lombard, here is this umbrella,
we will get it right now, have you ever
received such a beautiful gift from a salon,
you can see the branding inch, the
robbers have tolerated it, we will
definitely click here, friends,
so like, share and